{
    "subject": "resource/Secret_Sunshine",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Films_directed_by_Lee_Chang-dong",
    "human_readable": "The subject of Secret Sunshine is Category:Films directed by Lee Chang-dong.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8394994139671326,
            "question": "What is the category of Secret Sunshine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8162834048271179,
            "question": "Is Lee Chang-dong known for directing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8137800693511963,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Lee Chang-dong."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8061919808387756,
            "question": "Is Secret Sunshine a film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8020232915878296,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Lee Chang-dong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7855981588363647,
            "question": "Who directed Secret Sunshine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7318105101585388,
            "question": "Who is the director of Secret Sunshine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.588762104511261,
            "question": "Secret Sunshine falls under which category of media?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4855514466762543,
            "question": "What type of work is Secret Sunshine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40921032428741455,
            "question": "What genre does Secret Sunshine belong to?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of Secret Sunshine is Category:Films directed by Lee Chang-dong.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6812_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of work is Secret Sunshine?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6812_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Secret Sunshine falls under which category of media?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6812_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is the director of Secret Sunshine?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6812_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6812_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6812_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6812_129.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6812_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6812_161.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6812_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6812_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6812_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6812_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6812_72.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n**Triple:** Subject (Secret Sunshine) Category Films directed by Lee Chang-dong.\n\n**Evaluation:**\n\nThe documents provide information about the film \"Secret Sunshine\" and its director, Lee Chang-dong. According to the texts, Lee Chang-dong directed \"Secret Sunshine\", which is indeed a film. Therefore, the subject \"Secret Sunshine\" belongs to the category \"Films directed by Lee Chang-dong\".\n\n**JSON response:**\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly discuss the film \"Secret Sunshine,\" which was directed by Lee Chang-dong. Therefore, the statement that the subject of Secret Sunshine is in the category of films directed by Lee Chang-dong is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}